Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series XIX. Scheduling Office: Event files, 1998-2002 (Accession 40173)., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (Box 131-137)
  - The Software Factory grand opening, South Boston, VA, 1998 May 20 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Announcement of Don Upson as Secretary of Technology - press conference and reception, Vienna, VA, 1998 May 21 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Meeting with Bill Landsidle, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 21 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Northern Virginia Building Industry Association membership dinner meeting, Falls Church, VA, 1998 May 21 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Call from Japanese Counselor General, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 22 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Day program with the Dept. of Veterans' Affairs at McGuire Medical Center, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 22 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Call to Governor Patton (Kentucky) re: Tobacco Summit, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 22 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Abstinence Education media campaign press conference, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 22 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Call to Governor Beasley (South Carolina) re: Tobacco Summit, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - Meeting wth Ron Hamm re: Deputy Secretary of Natural Resources, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 24)
  - Meeting with David Dixon re: Dept. of Busisness Assistance, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 25)
  - Meeting with Gene Dishner re: Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 26)
  - Meeting with Shirley Ybarra re: Congestion and Mobility Summit, and Safety Service Patrol, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - Meeting with David Gehr re: Dept. of Transportation, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Teacher of the Year reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 27 (Box 132, Folder 29)
  - National Capital Region Congestion and Mobility Summit, Washington, DC, 1998 May 28 (Box 132, Folder 30)
  - Welcome to Governor's Fellows, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 28 (Box 132, Folder 31)
  - Phone call to Governor Zell Miller (Georgia) re: Tobacco Summit, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 28 (Box 132, Folder 32)
  - Meeting with Ken Wiegand re: Dept. of Aviation, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 28 (Box 132, Folder 33)
  - Helen Obenshain Newton Proclamation presentation, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 29 (Box 132, Folder 34)
  - Meeting with James Garner re: State Forester, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 28 (Box 132, Folder 35)
  - Meeting with Jack Kotvas re: Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 29 (Box 132, Folder 36)
  - Greeting Russell Nelson of the Mormon Church, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 30 (Box 132, Folder 37)
  - Car Tax bill signing ceremony, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 30 (Box 132, Folder 38)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth Advisory Committee meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 May 30 (Box 132, Folder 39)
  - Retirement ceremony for Addison Slayton (Dept. of Emergency Services), Richmond, VA, 1998 June 1 (Box 132, Folder 40)
  - Photo-ops of bill signings, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 1 (Box 132, Folder 41)
  - Meeting with Nick Taubman re: Destination Education, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 2 (Box 132, Folder 42)
  - Meeting with David Dickson re: Dept. of Business Administration, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 2 (Box 132, Folder 43)
  - Meeting with Carlton Courter re: Dept. of Agriculture, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 2 (Box 132, Folder 44)
  - Meeting with Tom Towberman re: Virginia Employment Commission, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 2 (Box 132, Folder 45)
  - Meeting with Rodney Phillips re: Virginia Milk Commission, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 2 (Box 132, Folder 46)
  - Meeting with Leo Bevon re: Dept. of Rail and Public Transportation, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 2 (Box 132, Folder 47)
  - Route I-895 Project bill signing, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 3 (Box 132, Folder 48)
  - Credit Rating Agencies luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 4 (Box 132, Folder 49)
  - Republican Party of Virginia Commonwealth Gala, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 4 (Box 132, Folder 50)
  - Public Employee of the Year Awards Presentation, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 5 (Box 132, Folder 51)
  - NASCAR Race - Pontiac Excitement 400, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 4 (Box 132, Folder 52)
  - Washington Post Online - Levey Live, Washington, DC, 1998 June 6 (Box 132, Folder 53)
  - Virginia Strategy Advisory Committee Kickoff meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 10 (Box 132, Folder 54)
  - Tobacco Summit Reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 10 (Box 132, Folder 55)
  - Maymont Foundation Reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 11 (Box 132, Folder 56)
  - Tobacco Summit, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 11 (Box 132, Folder 57)
  - Graduation of the 96th Basic Trooper Session, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 12 (Box 132, Folder 58)
  - Baan Co. U.S. Corporate Headquarters groundbreaking ceremony, Loudoun County, VA, 1998 June 12 (Box 132, Folder 59)
  - George C. Marshall Foundation interview, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 16 (Box 132, Folder 60)
  - Governor's Staff Reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 16 (Box 132, Folder 61)
  - New Partnership press conference, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 17 (Box 132, Folder 62)
  - Boys State, Lynchburg, VA, 1998 June 18 (Box 132, Folder 63)
  - Governor's Fellows Program, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 19 (Box 132, Folder 64)
  - Bill signing for Newport News Shipbuilding, Newport News, VA, 1998 June 19 (Box 132, Folder 65)
  - World Congress of Information Technology, Fairfax, VA, 1998 June 21-23 (Box 132, Folder 66)
  - Orbital announcement, Dulles, VA, 1998 June 23 (Box 132, Folder 67)
  - Meeting with Steve Case, Chairman and CEO of AOL, Reston, VA, 1998 June 23 (Box 132, Folder 68)
  - Meeting with Nancy Campbell and Dick Moe of the National Trust, Richmond, VA, 1998 July 1 (Box 132, Folder 69)
  - Girls State, Farmville, VA, 1998 June 24 (Box 132, Folder 70)
  - Economic Development luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 24 (Box 132, Folder 71)
  - Bill signing - SB 457 (Teen driving initiative), Richmond, VA, 1998 June 26 (Box 132, Folder 72)
  - Commission on Higher Education luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 June 30 (Box 132, Folder 73)
  - Luncheon with Mid-Atlantic Medical Services, Inc. (MAMSI) executives, Richmond, VA, 1998 July 1 (Box 132, Folder 74)
  - Meeting with Bill Barry re: Virginia Forward, Richmond, VA, 1998 July 23 (Box 132, Folder 75)
  - Youth Alcohol and Drug Abuse Prevention Project Summer Leadership Conference, Farmville, VA, 1998 July 24 (Box 132, Folder 76)
  - Regina Maersk reception, Norfolk, VA, 1998 July 25 (Box 132, Folder 77)
  - Meeting with Larry Silver re: Virginia Visitor Campus and Golf Resort, Richmond, VA, 1998 July 29 (Box 132, Folder 78)
  - Extraction Technologies, Governor's Opportunity Fund check presentation, Lawrenceville, VA, 1998 July 30 (Box 132, Folder 79)
  - VDOT Ribbon Cutting ceremeony at Riverview Industrial Park Interchange, Danville, VA, 1998 July 30 (Box 132, Folder 80)
  - Bassett Furniture, Governor's Opportunity Fund check presentation, Martinsville, VA, 1998 July 30 (Box 132, Folder 81)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History dinner honoring John Rocovich, Martinsville, VA, 1998 July 30 (Box 132, Folder 82)
  - National Governors' Association Conference, Milwaukee, WI, 1998 Aug 1-4 (folder 1 of 4) (Box 132, Folder 83)
  - National Governors' Association Conference, Milwaukee, WI, 1998 Aug 1-4 (folder 2 of 4) (Box 132, Folder 84)
  - National Governors' Association Conference, Milwaukee, WI, 1998 Aug 1-4 (folder 3 of 4) (Box 132, Folder 85)
  - National Governors' Association Conference, Milwaukee, WI, 1998 Aug 1-4 (folder 4 of 4) (Box 132, Folder 86)
  - Meeting with State Mental Health Facility Directors, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 5 (Box 132, Folder 87)
  - Governor's New Partnership Commission meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 6 (Box 132, Folder 88)
  - S and K Management Conference, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 11 (Box 132, Folder 89)
  - Tour of Bayview and surrounding area, Eastern Shore, 1998 Aug 11 (Box 132, Folder 90)
  - Meeting with Bill DeRusha re: Virginia Council on Economic Development, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 12 (Box 132, Folder 91)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Park II ribbon cutting ceremony, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 13 (Box 132, Folder 92)
  - Virginia AFL-CIO Convention, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Aug 14 (Box 132, Folder 93)
  - Report to Joint Money Committee, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 17 (Box 132, Folder 94)
  - Lunch and tour of Volvo New River Valley Assembly Plant, Dublin, VA, 1998 Aug 18 (Box 132, Folder 95)
  - Safe and Drug Free Schools check presentation, Wytheville, VA, 1998 Aug 18 (Box 132, Folder 96)
  - Economic Development announcement, Abingdon, VA, 1998 Aug 19 (Box 132, Folder 97)
  - Scott County Courthouse walk-through and picnic, Gate City, VA, 1998 Aug 19 (Box 132, Folder 98)
  - Red Onion Prison tour, Wise County, VA, 1998 Aug 19 (Box 132, Folder 99)
  - Happy Valley Recreation Park dinner, Clintwood, VA, 1998 Aug 19 (Box 132, Folder 100)
  - Appalachian School of Law tour and reception, Grundy, VA, 1998 Aug 20 (Box 132, Folder 101)
  - Smith Ridge Water Line Project dedication, Tazewell County, VA, 1998 Aug 20 (Box 132, Folder 102)
  - Smith Mountain Lake 4-H Education Center announcement and groundbreaking ceremony, Wirtz, VA, 1998 Aug 20 (Box 132, Folder 103)
  - SCHEV Board of Visitors training seminar, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 20 (Box 132, Folder 104)
  - Governor's Cup Golf Tournament pairings party, Kingsport, TN, 1998 Aug 22 (Box 132, Folder 105)
  - NASCAR Goody's 500, Bristol, VA, 1998 Aug 22 (Box 132, Folder 106)
  - Governor's Cup Golf Tournament, Bristol, VA, 1998 Aug 23 (Box 132, Folder 107)
  - Republican Governors Association Forum, Denver, CO, 1998 Aug 24 (Box 132, Folder 108)
  - Higher Education Commission meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 25 (Box 132, Folder 109)
  - Lorton Prison press conference, Lorton, VA, 1998 Aug 26 (Box 132, Folder 110)
  - Japanese External Trade Organization meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 27 (Box 132, Folder 111)
  - Council of Technology Services (COTS) meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 27 (Box 132, Folder 112)
  - SCC Pipeline Safety announcement, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 28 (Box 132, Folder 113)
  - Reception for Gilmore Campaign and Inaugural staff, Richmond, VA, 1998 Aug 28 (Box 132, Folder 114)
  - Meeting wih Thomas Fowlkes re: Virginia Economic Development Partnership, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 1 (Box 132, Folder 115)
  - Meeting with Donna Curry re: Higher Education, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 2 (Box 132, Folder 116)
  - Meeting with General Godwin re: Adjutant General, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 2 (Box 132, Folder 117)
  - Meeting with Mike Hardy of the Richmond Times Dispatch re: Mental Health, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 2 (Box 132, Folder 118)
  - Meeting with Claude Williams re: Adjutant General, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 2 (Box 132, Folder 119)
  - Terroism briefing, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 3 (Box 132, Folder 120)
  - Meeting with Jerry Simonoff re: Council on Information Management, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 3 (Box 132, Folder 121)
  - Meeting with Carroll Childers re: Adjutant General, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 3 (Box 132, Folder 122)
  - Interview with Richmond Magazine, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 4 (Box 132, Folder 123)
  - Radio interview with Richard Dollar, Richmond, vA, 1998 Sept 4 (Box 132, Folder 124)
  - Meeting with Conrad Helsley re: JMU Board of Visitors, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 4 (Box 132, Folder 125)
  - Meeting with Mark Mix re: JMU Board of Visitors, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 8 (Box 132, Folder 126)
  - Environmental Awards Presentation - Hopewell Community and Industry Panel, Hopewell, VA, 1998 Sept 8 (Box 132, Folder 127)
  - Meeting with Community Action Agencies, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 8 (Box 132, Folder 128)
  - Agency Head Retreat, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 9 (Box 132, Folder 129)
  - Meeting with Lewis Warren re: ODU Board of Visitors, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 9 (Box 132, Folder 130)
  - Meeting with Lloyd McDaniel re: Adjutant General, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 9 (Box 132, Folder 131)
  - Meeting with James Holden re: Adjutant General, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 9 (Box 132, Folder 132)
  - Reception for Congressman Frank Wolf, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 9 (Box 132, Folder 133)
  - Videotaping for Magila Project, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 10 (Box 132, Folder 134)
  - Breakfast for Demaris Miller, McLean, VA, 1998 Sept 10 (Box 132, Folder 135)
  - Dinner with Rusty Wallace, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 10 (Box 132, Folder 136)
  - Mental Health Commission meeting - Hammond Commission on Community Services and In-Patient Care, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 10 (Box 132, Folder 137)
  - State Central Committee luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 12 (Box 132, Folder 138)
  - NASCAR Race, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 12 (Box 132, Folder 139)
  - Wallops Island announcement - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Center, Wallops Island, VA, 1998 Sept 14 (Box 132, Folder 140)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch Editorial breakfast, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 15 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - American Council of Young Political Leaders Israeli Delegation, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 14 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Day on Capitol Hill, Washinton, DC, 1998 Sept 15 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Meeting with Bob Vila of This Old House, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 15 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Dinner with Southwest Virginia coal company owners, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 16 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Lunch with Patricia Cornwell, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 16 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - WRVA - Ask Governor Gilmore and public service announcements, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 17 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - NCT!Pac Retreat, Irvington, VA, 1998 Sept 18 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Cup polo match, Goochland, VA, 1998 Sept 20 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Meeting with Motorola executives, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 21 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Meeting with Ron Jordan re: Public Safety, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 21 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Town Hall Meeting preparation, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 21 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Second Annual Good Scout Technology Award luncheon, Vienna, VA, 1998 Sept 22 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Technology announcement and reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 22 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - NRA photo-op, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 23 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - State Employee Town Hall meeting, Roanoke, VA, 1998 Sept 23 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Small Business Innovation Research Program dinner, Blacksburg, VA, 1998 Sept 23 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - State Employee Town Hall meeting, Norfolk, VA, 1998 Sept 24 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Tourism Corporation reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 24 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - State Employee Town Hall meeting, Annandale, VA, 1998 Sept 24 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Meeting with Bill Keyes re: Governor's Employment and Training Dept., Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 25 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - State Employee Town Hall meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 25 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Henrico County Republican Committee's First Annual Fall Barbeque, Glen Allen, VA, 1998 Sept 26 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Wolftrap Associates Ball, Vienna, VA, 1998 Sept 26 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Project Exile dinner, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 27 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Commonwealth Council luncheon, Norfolk, VA, 1998 Sept 29 (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - State Fair - Commonwealth Day reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 Sept 29 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - Yupo Corporation grand opening, Chesapeake, VA, 1998 Sept 30 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - Rededication of the Lee Chapel and Museum at Washington and Lee University, Lexington, VA, 1998 Oct 3 (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - Southeast U.S. / Japan Association meeting, Mobile, AL, 1998 Oct 4-5 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Exile press conference, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 6 (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - Economic Development announcement - Hewlett-Packard, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 8 (Box 133, Folder 32)
  - Combined Virginia Campaign Kick-off, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 8 (Box 133, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Economic Development Prospect reception, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Oct 9 (Box 133, Folder 34)
  - Valentine Museum Centennial Celebration, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 10 (Box 133, Folder 35)
  - Air Products and Chemical Co. reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 14 (Box 133, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Transportation Conference, Lexington, VA, 1998 Oct 15 (Box 133, Folder 37)
  - Prevent Blindness dinner, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 15 (Box 133, Folder 38)
  - Obenshain Family brunch, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 17 (Box 133, Folder 39)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget Service Award Program, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 20 (Box 133, Folder 40)
  - Larry Sabato Roast to benefit the Center for Governmental Studies, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 20 (Box 133, Folder 41)
  - Greater Richmond Association of Commercial Real Estate luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 20 (Box 133, Folder 42)
  - Fall Crime Forum, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 21 (Box 133, Folder 43)
  - Press Conference with Bob Vila, Richmond, VA, 1998 Oct 28 (Box 133, Folder 44)
  - Prince William 66 Partnership Annual Meeting, Manassas, VA, 1998 Oct 28 (Box 133, Folder 45)
  - Bristol Compressors announcement, Bristol, VA, 1998 Oct 30 (Box 133, Folder 46)
  - Clerks Association meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 5 (Box 133, Folder 47)
  - Supreme Court dinner, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 5 (Box 133, Folder 48)
  - World Affairs Council of Greater Richmond luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 5 (Box 133, Folder 49)
  - Meeting with French Ambassador to the United States, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 5 (Box 133, Folder 50)
  - Oracle announcement, Reston, VA, 1998 Nov 6 (Box 133, Folder 51)
  - Virginia Business Council meeting, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 6 (Box 133, Folder 52)
  - Southeast U.S. / Korea Economic Committee - Virginia Reception, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Nov 7 (Box 133, Folder 53)
  - Southeast U.S. / Korea Economic Committee - Welcoming Reception, Norfolk, VA, 1998 Nov 8 (Box 133, Folder 54)
  - Southeast U.S. / Korea Economic Committee - Governor's Breakfast, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Nov 9 (Box 133, Folder 55)
  - American Legion Veterans Day Ceremony at the Virginia War Memorial, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 11 (Box 133, Folder 56)
  - Meeting with legislators, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 11 (Box 133, Folder 57)
  - Congressional Liaison meeting, Washington, DC, 1998 Nov (Box 133, Folder 58)
  - National Governors' Association seminar, Wilmington, DE, 1998 Nov 13 (Box 133, Folder 59)
  - Virginia State Conference NAACP Annual Convention membership luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 13 (Box 133, Folder 60)
  - Centenarian birthday party, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 13 (Box 133, Folder 61)
  - Children's Hospital Ball, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 13 (Box 133, Folder 62)
  - National Rifle Association Celebrate Virginia reception, Fairfax, VA, 1998 Nov 16 (Box 133, Folder 63)
  - MCI/WorldCom announcement, Loudoun, VA, 1998 Nov 24 (Box 133, Folder 64)
  - Indian Tax Tribute, Richmond, VA, 1998 Nov 25 (Box 133, Folder 65)
  - Commission on Information Technology - Dinner, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Dec 1 (Box 133, Folder 66)
  - Commission on Inforamtion Technology - Meeting, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Dec 2 (Box 133, Folder 67)
  - Family Foundation Gala Awards and Benefit Banquet, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 3 (Box 133, Folder 68)
  - Environmental Announcement - Water Quality, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 7 (Box 133, Folder 69)
  - Chesapeake Bay Executive Council meeting, Baltimore, MD, 1998 Dec 8 (Box 133, Folder 70)
  - Virginia Strategy for Economic Development Rollout luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 9 (Box 133, Folder 71)
  - Virginia Tourism Authority announcement, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 10 (Box 133, Folder 72)
  - Rural Economic Development announcement, Abingdon, VA, 1998 Dec 11 (Box 133, Folder 73)
  - Governor's Holiday Reception and Dinner, Williamsburg, VA, 1998 Dec 12 (Box 133, Folder 74)
  - Governor's Holiday Open House, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 19 (Box 133, Folder 75)
  - Governor's Holiday Dinner, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 19 (Box 133, Folder 76)
  - Fredericksburg Tourism announcemnt, Fredericksburg, VA, 1998 Dec 21 (Box 133, Folder 77)
  - Governor's Holiday Reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 21 (Box 133, Folder 78)
  - Governor's Staff Reception, Richmond, VA, 1998 Dec 22 (Box 133, Folder 79)
  - Henrico Business Council luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 6 (Box 133, Folder 80)
  - Press conference, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 6 (Box 133, Folder 81)
  - Lieutenant Governor's reception and dinner, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 7 (Box 133, Folder 82)
  - Technology meetings, Las Vegas, NV, 1999 Jan 8 (Box 133, Folder 83)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation meeting, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 11 (Box 133, Folder 84)
  - Commonwealth Prayer Breakfast, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 14 (Box 133, Folder 85)
  - Virginia Federation of Republican Women Legislative Day luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 14 (Box 133, Folder 86)
  - Sussex II State Prison opening ceremony, Waverly, VA, 1999 Jan 18 (Box 133, Folder 87)
  - Thomas Jefferson Institute for Public Policy reception (folder 1 of 2), Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 19 (Box 133, Folder 88)
  - Thomas Jefferson Institute for Public Policy reception (folder 2 of 2), Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 19 (Box 133, Folder 89)
  - Y2K Summit / Year 2000 Leadership Summit, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 22 (Box 133, Folder 90)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference, Arlington, VA, 1999 Jan 23 (Box 133, Folder 91)
  - Journal Newspapers Progress Business luncheon, Fairfax, VA, 1999 Jan 26 (Box 133, Folder 92)
  - Fraternal Order of Police Rally Day, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 27 (Box 133, Folder 93)
  - Energy Recovery / Eastern Shore economic announcement, Northampton County, VA, 1999 Jan 29 (Box 133, Folder 94)
  - Phone call to Marriot International, Inc., Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 29 (Box 133, Folder 95)
  - Virginians for Black Inclusion in Government reception, Richmond, VA, 1999 Jan 29 (Box 133, Folder 96)
  - Government Performance Project press conference, Washington, DC, 1999 Feb 1 (Box 133, Folder 97)
  - States' Terrorism Policy Summit, Williamsburg, VA, 1999 Feb 2 (Box 133, Folder 98)
  - Governor Godwin Memorial Service, Chuckatuck, VA, 1999 Feb 2 (Box 133, Folder 99)
  - Eternal Technoligy announcement, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 4 (Box 133, Folder 100)
  - Gateway Company announcement, Hampton, VA, 1999 Feb 5 (Box 133, Folder 101)
  - Black Tie dinner at the Executive Mansion, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 5 (Box 133, Folder 102)
  - Capital One announcement, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 9 (Box 133, Folder 103)
  - Center for Innovative Technology Board Meeting, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 10 (Box 133, Folder 104)
  - Chesapeake Student Leadership Forum, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 10 (Box 133, Folder 105)
  - Virginia Alliance for the Mentally Ill Annual Tribute Dinner, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 11 (Box 133, Folder 106)
  - Virginia Tobacco Conference and Trade Show, Halifax County, VA, 1999 Feb 13 (Box 133, Folder 107)
  - Mount Vernon Celebration, Fairfax, VA, 1999 Feb 15 (Box 133, Folder 108)
  - Lunch with Rear Admiral Paul Gaffney, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 16 (Box 133, Folder 109)
  - State Council on Higher Education in Virginia Outstanding Faculty awards ceremony and luncheon, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb (Box 133, Folder 110)
  - Black History Month event, Richmond, VA, 1999 Feb 18 (Box 133, Folder 111)
  - A.T. Massey Coal Company Annual Reception and Banquet, Charleston, WVA, 1999 Feb 25 (Box 133, Folder 112)
  - Elegant Culinary Affaire to benefit Hospice Support Care of Williamsburg, Williamsburg, VA, 1999 Feb 28 (Box 133, Folder 113)
  - Washington Post - Springfield Plant Expansion Ceremony, Fairfax, VA, 1999 Mar 1 (Box 133, Folder 114)
  - Meeting with Baltimore / Washington Olympic Committee, Richmond, VA, 1999 Mar 3 (Box 133, Folder 115)
  - H.P. Hood announcement, Winchester, VA, 1999 Mar 4 (Box 133, Folder 116)
  - Virginia Advanced Shipbuilding and Carrier Integration Center Groundbreaking, Newport News, VA, 1999 Mar 9 (Box 133, Folder 117)
  - AOL announcement, Prince William, VA, 1999 Mar 10 (Box 133, Folder 118)